[
    {
        "question": "Þæs (Biscop) #### stan",
        "correctAnswer": "biscopas",
        "explanation":"Here 'biscop' is in the genitive so it takes the 'as' ending",
        "commonMistakes": [
            {
                "badAnswer": "Wrong Answer 1",
                "explanation": "Here's why it's wrong."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The (cyning) #### Ferth Thaem Beorgum",
        "correctAnswer": "cyning|kyning",
        "explanation":"asfasf",        
        "commonMistakes": [
            {
                "badanswer": "Wrong Answer 2",
                "explanation": "Here's why it's wrong."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "3. Þæs (Biscop) #### stan",
        "correctAnswer": "biscopas",
        "explanation":"Here 'biscop' is in the genitive so it takes the 'as' ending",
        "commonMistakes": [
            {
                "badAnswer": "Wrong Answer 1",
                "explanation": "Here's why it's wrong."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "4. Þæs (Biscop) #### stan",
        "correctAnswer": "biscopas",
        "explanation":"Here 'biscop' is in the genitive so it takes the 'as' ending",
        "commonMistakes": [
            {
                "badAnswer": "Wrong Answer 1",
                "explanation": "Here's why it's wrong."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "5. Þæs (Biscop) #### stan",
        "correctAnswer": "biscopas",
        "explanation":"Here 'biscop' is in the genitive so it takes the 'as' ending",
        "commonMistakes": [
            {
                "badAnswer": "Wrong Answer 1",
                "explanation": "Here's why it's wrong."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "6. Þæs (Biscop) #### stan",
        "correctAnswer": "biscopas",
        "explanation":"Here 'biscop' is in the genitive so it takes the 'as' ending",
        "commonMistakes": [
            {
                "badAnswer": "Wrong Answer 1",
                "explanation": "Here's why it's wrong."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "7. Þæs (Biscop) #### stan",
        "correctAnswer": "biscopas",
        "explanation":"Here 'biscop' is in the genitive so it takes the 'as' ending",
        "commonMistakes": [
            {
                "badAnswer": "Wrong Answer 1",
                "explanation": "Here's why it's wrong."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "8. Þæs (Biscop) #### stan",
        "correctAnswer": "biscopas",
        "explanation":"Here 'biscop' is in the genitive so it takes the 'as' ending",
        "commonMistakes": [
            {
                "badAnswer": "Wrong Answer 1",
                "explanation": "Here's why it's wrong."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "9. Þæs (Biscop) #### stan",
        "correctAnswer": "biscopas",
        "explanation":"Here 'biscop' is in the genitive so it takes the 'as' ending",
        "commonMistakes": [
            {
                "badAnswer": "Wrong Answer 1",
                "explanation": "Here's why it's wrong."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "10. Seo (Cwene) #### Ferth Thaem Beorgum",
        "correctAnswer": "sfasfasfsa",
        "explanation":"asfasf",        
        "commonMistakes": [
            {
                "badanswer": "Wrong Answer 3",
                "explanation": "Here's why it's wrong."
            }
        ]
    }
]



